const quiz1data = [
    {
      question: "I ___ work at 8.30 most days.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "start", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "am starting", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'We use present simple to talk about habits or things that happen on a regular basis.'
   },
    {
      question: "Water ___ at 100 degrees Celsius.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "is boiling", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "boils", isCorrect: true}
      ],
      help: 'We use present simple to talk about things that are always true. ',
      help1: '-most verbs: add s. play-plays  3rd  person singular '
   },
    {
      question: "'Where is Jane?' 'She ___ a shower.'",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "is having", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "has", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'The action is happening at the time of speaking.'
   },
    {
      question: "I ___ coffee every morning",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "drink", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "am drinking", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'We use the present simple to talk about habits or things we do regularly.'
   },
    {
      question: "The population of the world ___ very fast.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "increases", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "is increasing", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: 'We use the present continuous when we talk about a change that has started to happen.'
   },
    {
      question: "Bob ___ football every weekend.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "plays", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "is playing", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'We use the present simple to talk about something that happens regularly in the present.'
   },
    {
      question: "My brother ___ in London for few weeks.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "is living", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "lives", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'We use the present continuous to talk about temporary situations.'
   },
    {
      question: "Each summer I __ to Greece for a holiday.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "go", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "am going", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'We use the present simple to talk about habits or things that happen on a regular basis.'
   },
    {
      question: "Sally ___ better and better at speaking Spanish.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "is getting", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "gets", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'We use the present continuous to talk about situations which are slowly changing.'
   },
    {
      question: "Alice ___ the piano brilliantly.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "plays", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "is playing", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'We use the present simple to describe things that are always true, or situations that exist now and, as far as we know, will go on indefinitely.'
   },
    {
      question: "My sister ___ with the dog in the garden right now.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "is playing", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "plays", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'We use the present continuous to talk about things which are happening at the moment of speaking.'
   },
    {
      question: "The Earth ___ round the Sun.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "goes", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "is going", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'We use present simple to talk about things that are always true.'
   }
  ]
export default quiz1data
